Lois Gibbs Love Canal Papers MS063
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Subject files, circa 1951 -- 2007; MS063.001; 19.2 Linear Feet 16 record cartons
  - LCHA letters of thanks, 1978 -- 1980; MS063.001.006.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Lois Gibb's speaking engagements and television and radio interviews, circa 1980; MS063.001.006.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Injunction papers, circa 1979 -- 1980; MS063.001.006.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Love Canal Homeowners Association letterhead, circa 1965 -- 2007; MS063.001.006.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Love Canal maps, circa 1965 -- 2007; MS063.001.006.00018; 2 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 18-19)
  - Petitions to remove Mayor Michael O'Laughlin from the Revitalization Committee, circa 1980; MS063.001.006.00019; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Love Canal resident addresses, circa 1965 -- 2007; MS063.001.006.00020; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Civil actions against Hooker Chemicals and Plastics Corporation and other entities, circa 1965 -- 2007; MS063.001.006.00021; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Civil actions against Hooker Chemicals and Plastics Corporation and other entities, circa 1965 -- 2007; MS063.001.006.00022; 3 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 23-25)
  - Newspaper clippings, circa 1965 -- 1977; MS063.001.006.00023; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Newspaper clippings about New York children births, circa 1980; MS063.001.006.00024; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Love Canal Medical Trust, 1995; MS063.001.006.00025; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Love Canal and Love Canal Revitalization Agency, 1994 -- 1996; MS063.001.006.00026; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Love Canal lawsuit, 1994 -- 1995; MS063.001.006.00027; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Ron Simon, 1989 -- 1995; MS063.001.006.00028; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Anne Rabe/New York Environmental Institute, 1989; MS063.001.006.00029; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Community group contact, circa 1965 -- 2007; MS063.001.006.00030; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Governor Cuomo, 1989 -- 1990; MS063.001.006.00031; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Abrams/Attorney General's office, circa 1989 -- 1990; MS063.001.006.00032; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Hinchey, Maurice, 1988 -- 1990; MS063.001.006.00033; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Occidental Chemical Corporation, 1988 -- 1990; MS063.001.007.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Occidental Petroleum Corporation annual reports, 1989; MS063.001.007.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Occidental Corporation clean-up, 1989 -- 1990; MS063.001.007.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Environmental Protection Agency general/correspondence, 1988 -- 1990; MS063.001.007.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Environmental Protection Agency, Reilly, 1989 -- 1990; MS063.001.007.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Environmental Protection Agency inspector general, 1989; MS063.001.007.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Axelrod/Department of Health, circa 1978 -- 1979, 1988 -- 1991; MS063.001.007.00007; 2 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 7-8)
  - Entertainment industry, 1989; MS063.001.007.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Letters to the editor, circa 1978 -- 1990; MS063.001.007.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Maps, circa 1986 -- 1987; MS063.001.007.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - 93rd Street school, 1990; MS063.001.007.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Control 225, 1989; MS063.001.007.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Feasibility study/workshop, circa 1986 -- 1987; MS063.001.007.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Slide of a building, photographed by M. Heimon, 1990; MS063.001.007.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Habitability study, circa 1985 -- 1989; MS063.001.007.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Housing/Housing and Urban Dev, 1988 -- 1990; MS063.001.007.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Environmental impact study for New York, 1990; MS063.001.007.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Love Canal banks, circa 1990 -- 1992; MS063.001.007.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Land use study July 1989 comments, circa 1989 -- 1990; MS063.001.007.00019; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Richard J. Lippes, 1984 -- 1985; MS063.001.007.00020; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Love Canal feasibility study, 1987; MS063.001.007.00021; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Current fact sheets, circa 1990; MS063.001.007.00022; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Love Canal Revitalization Agency/Carr, 1989 -- 1990; MS063.001.007.00023; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - California Proposition 65, 1987 -- 1989; MS063.001.007.00024; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - October 1990 action, circa 1990; MS063.001.007.00025; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - September 1990 rally (Albany), circa 1989 -- 1990; MS063.001.007.00026; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - April 1990 event notice, circa 1989 -- 1990; MS063.001.007.00027; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - April 1990 correspondents, circa 1989 -- 1990; MS063.001.007.00028; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Habitability study and Superfund correspondence, 1989; MS063.001.007.00029; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - September/November 1989 rallies, MS063.001.007.00030; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Index cards, circa 1965 -- 2007; MS063.001.007.00031; 2 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 32-33)
  - Governor Cuomo campaign supporters, circa 1990; MS063.001.008.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - New York Freedom of Information requests on Love Canal, 1990; MS063.001.008.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Love Canal resettlement fact sheets, circa 1990; MS063.001.008.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Love Canal resettlement testimonies, 1989 -- 1990; MS063.001.008.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Love Canal discussion paper and newspaper clippings, circa 1986; MS063.001.008.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Indexes and other material, circa 1965 -- 2007; MS063.001.008.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Love Canal index cards, circa 1965 -- 2007; MS063.001.008.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 7)
    Scans of index cards.
  - "609…and Counting: Hazardous Wastes and the Public's Health in New York State," by Thomas Bartosiewicz, 1980; MS063.001.008.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Table of contents and notes, circa 1965 -- 2007; MS063.001.008.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - History of Canal by David Parry, 1976; MS063.001.008.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Hooker Chemical Company, circa 1978 -- 1981; MS063.001.008.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Department of Social Services memorandum and Love Canal Task Force bulletin, circa 1978; MS063.001.008.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Deeds/patents, circa 1951 -- 1971; MS063.001.008.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Testimony and Fred C. Hart Associates, Inc. report, circa 1978; MS063.001.008.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Lois Gibbs newspaper clippings, 1978; MS063.001.008.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Love Canal chronology LCHA, circa 1978 -- 1980; MS063.001.008.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - LCHA - laundry lists, circa 1978 -- 1980; MS063.001.008.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Memos, 1978 -- 1980; MS063.001.008.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Letters to editor, circa 1980; MS063.001.008.00019; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - LCHA newsletters, circa 1979 -- 1980; MS063.001.008.00020; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - LCHA daily logs, circa 1980; MS063.001.008.00021; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - LCHA, circa 1978 -- 1980; MS063.001.008.00022; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - LCHA correspondence, circa 1978 -- 1980; MS063.001.008.00023; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Gibbs's testimony, circa 1978 -- 1979; MS063.001.008.00024; 2 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 24-25)
  - "Project Statement: Love Canal Remedial Action Project", circa 1978; MS063.001.008.00025; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Construction - accidents, circa 1978 -- 1979; MS063.001.008.00026; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Demonstration grant, 1979; MS063.001.008.00027; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Safety plans, circa 1978 -- 1979; MS063.001.008.00028; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Engineer's daily diary, 1979; MS063.001.008.00029; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Love Canal storm sewer decontamination, circa 1980; MS063.001.008.00030; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Treatment plant data, circa 1978; MS063.001.008.00031; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Monitoring wells, circa 1978 -- 1980; MS063.001.008.00032; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - "Comments on the Love Canal pollution abatement plan," by Charles H.V. Ebert, 1979; MS063.001.008.00033; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Love Canal Remedial Action Plan memorandums, circa 1978 -- 1979; MS063.001.008.00034; 1 Folder(s) (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Doctors' letters individual, 1974 -- 1979; MS063.001.009.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Blood mercury, circa 1965 -- 2007; MS063.001.009.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Birth defects, circa 1965 -- 2007; MS063.001.009.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Health study questionnaires, circa 1978; MS063.001.009.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 4)
    Questionnaires are blank.
  - Cleveland Clinic correspondence, circa 1979 -- 1980; MS063.001.009.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - National Institute of Environmental Health Sciences Data (NIEHS) /Reports/Department of Health, Education, and Welfare (DEW), circa 1978 -- 1979; MS063.001.009.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Dr. Nicholas J. Vianna correspondence, 1979 -- 1980; MS063.001.009.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Growth study directories and fliers, circa 1978 -- 1980; MS063.001.009.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Growth study fliers and questionnaires, circa 1978 -- 1980; MS063.001.009.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Hotel lists, circa 1978 -- 1980; MS063.001.009.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Temporary relocation, circa 1979; MS063.001.009.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Relocation forms, circa 1979; MS063.001.009.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Federal Emergency Management Association (FEMA)/FDAA correspondence and status report, circa 1979 -- 1980; MS063.001.009.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Tom Frey correspondence, circa 1978; MS063.001.009.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - HUD, circa 1979; MS063.001.009.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Revitalization, circa 1979 -- 1980; MS063.001.009.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Environmental Defense Fund (EDF), circa 1979-1980; MS063.001.009.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Subcommittee on the Potential Health Effects of Toxic Chemical Dumps, circa 1980; MS063.001.009.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Adeline G. Levine articles, circa 1979; MS063.001.009.00019; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Indexes, circa 1965 -- 2007; MS063.001.009.00020; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - "The Silent Sympathy: A Study of Attitudes Toward Spontaneous Abortion," by Dorothy Hai and Donald Sullivan, circa 1980 -- 1982; MS063.001.009.00021; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - EPA memo (to citizens) and correspondence, circa 1980; MS063.001.009.00022; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - City of Niagara Falls letter, 1980; MS063.001.009.00023; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Radiation analysis, 1979; MS063.001.009.00024; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Vegetation mortality correspondence and memorandums, 1979; MS063.001.009.00025; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Weather and health data, circa 1978 -- 1980; MS063.001.009.00026; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Chemical migration sampling plan, circa 1978; MS063.001.009.00027; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Chemicals identified at Canal, circa 1978 -- 1980; MS063.001.009.00028; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - 93rd Street school, 1978 -- 1979; MS063.001.009.00029; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Wheatfield/103rd Street soil and water analytical reports, 1979; MS063.001.009.00030; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - EPA Carcinogen Assessment Group (CAG) results, 1978 -- 1979; MS063.001.009.00031; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - 3LC 203.1 DEC Love Canal treatabilities studies, 1979; MS063.001.009.00032; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - DOH air data, circa 1978; MS063.001.009.00033; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - New York State Department of Health air sampling data, 1978; MS063.001.009.00034; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Soil analysis, 1979; MS063.001.009.00035; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - New York State Department of Health air sampling data, circa 1978; MS063.001.009.00036; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Storm sewers, circa 1968 -- 1978; MS063.001.009.00037; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Earth Dimensions, Inc. soil reports and data, 1979; MS063.001.009.00038; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Sump data, circa 1978; MS063.001.009.00039; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Environmental Protection Agency and New York State Department of Health data and memorandums, 1978 -- 1979; MS063.001.009.00040; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Love Canal groundwater report from Calspan, 1977; MS063.001.009.00041; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Analytical results (misc.), 1978 -- 1979; MS063.001.009.00042; 1 Folder(s) (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - EPA - monitoring program, 1980; MS063.001.010.00001; 2 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 1-2)
  - Environmental Protection Agency - monitoring program, circa 1978 -- 1980; MS063.001.010.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Doug Costle and EPA correspondence, 1979 -- 1980; MS063.001.010.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - EPA Love Canal data, circa 1978; MS063.001.010.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - "Preliminary Report of the New York State Assembly Task Force on Toxic Substances: Inquiry into the Love Canal and Related Matters", 1980; MS063.001.010.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - John J. LaFalce correspondence and press releases, circa 1979 -- 1981; MS063.001.010.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Legislation, federal, 1979; MS063.001.010.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Legislation, state, 1979 -- 1980; MS063.001.010.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Testimonies, 1979; MS063.001.010.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Court actions and testimony, circa 1979; MS063.001.010.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Civil actions and affidavits, circa 1978 -- 1979; MS063.001.010.00011; 2 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 12-13)
  - Love Canal clippings, 1979; MS063.001.010.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1979 --1980; MS063.001.010.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Lester report drafts, circa 1965 -- 2007; MS063.001.010.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Lester report drafts, circa 1965 -- 2007; MS063.001.010.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Lester report drafts, circa 1965 -- 2007; MS063.001.010.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - "Science" and chromosome study correspondence, circa 1980 -- 1981; MS063.001.010.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Letters to Lois Gibbs and the Love Canal Homeowners Association, 1980; MS063.001.010.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Letters, circa 1980; MS063.001.010.00019; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence, 1979 -- 1980; MS063.001.010.00020; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - T-shirt purchasing correspondence, circa 1980; MS063.001.010.00021; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Love Canal information requests, circa 1980; MS063.001.010.00022; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence, circa 1978 -- 1980; MS063.001.010.00023; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Love Canal newspaper clippings, circa 1980 -- 1981; MS063.001.010.00024; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Love Canal and EPA newspaper clippings, circa 1979 -- 1983; MS063.001.010.00025; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Growth study and hazardous waste newspaper clippings, 1982; MS063.001.010.00026; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Love Canal health data and Lois Gibbs correspondence, circa 1979 -- 1980; MS063.001.011.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Love Canal newspaper clippings, 1983; MS063.001.011.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - "Love Canal: A Bibliography," by Marja I. Hart, Jeannine A. Lee, and James K. Webster, 1979; MS063.001.011.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - NOVA program, 1979; MS063.001.011.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Hazardous waste newspaper clippings and article, circa 1978 -- 1981; MS063.001.011.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Newspaper clippings, circa 1980 -- 1983; MS063.001.011.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - David Axelrod and Mayor Michael O'Laughlin impeachment petitions, circa 1965 -- 2007; MS063.001.011.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Nurse practitioner survey forms, circa 1965 -- 2007; MS063.001.011.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - North Smithfield Ecology Festival poster, 1980; MS063.001.011.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Map of waste disposal sites of the Niagara-Erie region, 1979; MS063.001.011.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - "Love Canal Remedial Action Project: Central Sector", circa 1979; MS063.001.011.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Notes and directories, circa 1978; MS063.001.011.00012; 3 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 12-14)
  - "Love Canal Remedial Action project: Monitoring Well Installation and Sampling", 1979; MS063.001.011.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - "Love Canal Remedial Action Project: Central Sector", 1979; MS063.001.011.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous notes, circa 1979 -- 1980; MS063.001.011.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - "Toxic Substances in New York's Environment: An Interim Report", 1979; MS063.001.011.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - New York State's handling of Love Canal, circa 1965 -- 2007; MS063.001.011.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Index, circa 1965 -- 2007; MS063.001.011.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - "The Remedial Construction Project at Love Canal, Niagara Falls, New York: Findings and Comments", 1980; MS063.001.011.00019; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Love Canal figures, circa 1978 -- 1980; MS063.001.011.00020; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Comments on remedial construction report, circa 1980; MS063.001.011.00021; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1983; MS063.001.011.00022; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - "Health problems and chemical correlation", circa 1965 -- 2007; MS063.001.011.00023; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Love Canal resident health advertisement and questionnaire, circa 1965 -- 2007; MS063.001.011.00024; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - "Toxic Substances in New York's Environment: Appendices", 1979; MS063.001.011.00025; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - "Interagency Task Force on Hazardous Wastes: Draft Report", 1979; MS063.001.011.00026; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - "Interagency Task Force on Hazardous Wastes: Hearing Officer's Report", 1979; MS063.001.011.00027; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - "Love Canal Emergency Declaration Area: Proposed Habitability Criteria", 1986; MS063.001.011.00028; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Love Canal Lawsuit/EPA correspondence, circa 1978 – 1991; MS063.001.012.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Love Canal lawsuits and Love Canal resettlement/rehabitability, circa 1990 – 1992; MS063.001.012.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Love Canal Area Revitalization Agency and the Love Canal habitability study, 1980, 1988 – 1992; MS063.001.012.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Occidental Chemical Corporation lawsuits, 1994; MS063.001.012.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Love Canal Medical Fund correspondence and resumes, circa 1990; MS063.001.012.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Civil action against Occidental Chemical Corporation and other entities, circa 1989; MS063.001.012.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Chromosome health studies, circa 1980 – 1983; MS063.001.012.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence and newspaper clippings, circa 1988 – 1995; MS063.001.012.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Hazardous waste and the Love Canal resettlement newspaper clippings, circa 1988 – 1992; MS063.001.012.00009; 3 Folder(s) (Box 12, Folder 9-11)
  - Other Love Canal trust fund, 1995; MS063.001.012.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Local physicians and clinical laboratories, circa 1978 -- 1980; MS063.001.012.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Love Canal follow-up health study, circa 1965 -- 2007; MS063.001.012.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Love Canal Medical Fund beneficiary surveys, 2001; MS063.001.012.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Love Canal Medical Fund correspondence and newsletters, circa 2002; MS063.001.012.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Love Canal Medical Fund correspondence and newsletters, circa 1988 -- 2001; MS063.001.012.00015; 2 Folder(s) (Box 12, Folder 17-18)
  - Love Canal Medical Fund correspondence and medical benefit plans, circa 1996 -- 1999; MS063.001.012.00016; 2 Folder(s) (Box 12, Folder 19-20)
  - Love Canal Medical Fund and the Love Canal follow-up health study correspondence, 1996 -- 2000; MS063.001.013.00001; 2 Folder(s) (Box 13, Folder 1-2)
  - Love Canal Medical Fund correspondence and minutes, circa 1985 -- 1989; MS063.001.013.00002; 3 Folder(s) (Box 13, Folder 3-5)
  - Love Canal Medical Fund correspondence and minutes, circa 1996; MS063.001.013.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Love Canal Revitalization Agency newspaper clippings and newsletters, circa 1999; MS063.001.013.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Love Canal Medical Fund newsletters, Spring 1999; MS063.001.013.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Love Canal resettlement newspaper clippings, circa 1990 -- 1999; MS063.001.013.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Lois Gibbs's interviews and media appearances, circa 1994 -- 1998; MS063.001.013.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Love Canal Medical Fund correspondence and annual report, 2000 -- 2004; MS063.001.013.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Love Canal Medical Fund correspondence and reports, circa 1990 -- 1994; MS063.001.013.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Center for Health, Environment and Justice and the Environmental Support Center financial records and memorandums, circa 1998 -- 1999; MS063.001.013.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 13, Folder 13)
    Original folder title: 'Loose items from "Miner Workshop Collection' -- possibly given to Peabody Essex Museum + U. Michigan Archives (see notes inside)"
  - Environmental Support Center correspondence and financial records, circa 1996 -- 1998; MS063.001.013.00011; 2 Folder(s) (Box 13, Folder 14-15)
  - Environmental Support Center financial statements, 1990 -- 1993; MS063.001.013.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Environmental Support Center memorandums, circa 1994 -- 1998; MS063.001.013.00013; 3 Folder(s) (Box 13, Folder 17-19)
  - Environmental Support Center annual report and memorandum, 1996; MS063.001.013.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Environmental Support Center financial records and memorandums, 1995 -- 1998; MS063.001.013.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Environmental Support Center minutes, 1996 -- 1997; MS063.001.013.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Environmental Support Center 2000 - 2005 strategic plan, 2001; MS063.001.013.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 13, Folder 23)